<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MechTech</string>


    <string name="headlights"> Illuminate the road ahead with our high-quality headlights,
        designed for optimal visibility and safety. Explore a range of styles,
        from sleek LED headlights to powerful halogen options!</string>
    <string name="bumper"> Crafted for durability and style, our bumpers are designed to withstand the
        demands of the road while enhancing the overall look of your ride.</string>


    <string name="breaklights"> Engineered for durability and performance,
        our brake lights provide reliable stopping power while adding a
        touch of elegance to your ride</string>


    <string name="wipers">Ensure clear visibility in any weather with our top-quality windshield wipers.
        From heavy rain to snow and sleet, our wipers are designed to keep your
        windshield streak-free and crystal clear.
    </string>


    <string name="tyre">Revitalize your ride with our premium selection of tires.
        From all-season versatility to high-performance options,
        our extensive range caters to every driving need.</string>


    <string name="rims"> Crafted with precision and durability in mind,
        our rims not only enhance the visual appeal of your
        ride but also provide optimal performance.</string>


    <string name="plugs">Engineered for compatibility and durability, our car plugs are a must-have for modern drivers
   </string>
    <string name="shocks">Transform your driving experience with our premium shock absorbers.
        Engineered for performance and comfort.
    </string>
    <string name="turbo">Unleash the power of performance with our premium turbochargers.
        Elevate your driving experience by adding a turbocharger to your engine,
        boosting horsepower and torque for exhilarating acceleration.</string>

    <string name="sidemirror"> Replace damaged or outdated mirrors with our high-quality options
        that not only provide a clear view of your surroundings
        but also add a touch of elegance to your ride.</string>


</resources>